<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Typhoon Network Archive</title><link>https://archive.typhoon.network/</link><description>Recent content on Typhoon Network Archive</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 02:25:59 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://archive.typhoon.network/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>On Matthew Albright, Sonar and getting $200,000 stolen</title><link>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/on-sonar-whalespring-matthew-albright-and-getting-300-000-stolen-our-side-of-the-story-fe89ff100f67/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 May 2021 02:25:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/on-sonar-whalespring-matthew-albright-and-getting-300-000-stolen-our-side-of-the-story-fe89ff100f67/</guid><description>This story has originally appeared on https://typhoonnetwork.medium.com/on-sonar-whalespring-matthew-albright-and-getting-300-000-stolen-our-side-of-the-story-fe89ff100f67
On 8th of May, our strategic partner WhaleSpring/Sonar, more specifically the person in charge Matthew Albright, made the decision to market-sell 2,000,000 TYPH tokens (resulting in actual $200,000 USD out of $560,000 USD worth) we have allocated to them as part of our partnership deal, crashing the TYPH token price and damaging investor trust.
We have not received information about this beforehand and no attempt to discuss any ongoing problems has been made prior.</description></item><item><title>Typhoon Network Digest — 2021CW16</title><link>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/hi-and-welcome-to-this-weeks-edition-of-the-typhoon-network-a421937cf9c5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2021 14:35:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/hi-and-welcome-to-this-weeks-edition-of-the-typhoon-network-a421937cf9c5/</guid><description>This story has originally appeared on https://medium.com/@typhoonnetwork/hi-and-welcome-to-this-weeks-edition-of-the-typhoon-network-a421937cf9c5
Hi and welcome to this weeks edition of the Typhoon Network digest.
This week has been great to the Typhoon ecosystem in general, so much has been going on behind the curtains to ensure the LONG success of $TYPH. Here is a sneak peek of what has happen this week.
This weeks highlights Typhoon Network is now available on CoinStats, Delta and LiveCoinWatch Typhoon Network is listed on CoinGecko Strategic partnership with Sonar / WhaleSpring announced Successfully hired a Fullstack Engineer and onboarded him to the team, finished converting our mods into paid Community Managers Expanded international reach with new telegram subgroups Meme contest launched We’ve announced our first centralized exchange listing: CoinTiger We have also been featured on a blog written by sicario, a known blogger, where we provided some insights into our vision.</description></item><item><title>Typhoon Network Digest — 2021CW15</title><link>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/typhoon-network-digest-2021cw15-1c1ee6077080/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2021 02:11:03 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/typhoon-network-digest-2021cw15-1c1ee6077080/</guid><description>This story has originally appeared on https://medium.com/@typhoonnetwork/typhoon-network-digest-2021cw15-1c1ee6077080
Hi and welcome to the third Typhoon Network digest. If you haven’t yet, check-out the previous entries to get up-to-speed with how the project is doing.
This week main topics summarized:
Typhoon partnered with beefy.finance and added a self-compounding vault A second staking pool has been released The Airdrop claim has been released to mainnet Typhoon has successfully been audited (Report here) Updates on hiring and team structure (see below) On app volume &amp;amp; token price As of today, Typhoon has transacted $413,142 in 7d Volume.</description></item><item><title>Typhoon Network Digest — Post-IFO Edition</title><link>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/typhoon-network-digest-post-ifo-edition-beca0bfcfc09/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 02:00:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/typhoon-network-digest-post-ifo-edition-beca0bfcfc09/</guid><description>This story has originally appeared on https://medium.com/@typhoonnetwork/typhoon-network-digest-post-ifo-edition-beca0bfcfc09
Hi and welcome to the second Typhoon Network digest. Last time we were right before the IFO. It’s been roughly a week since then, so what happened?
Here’s a quick summary :
We finished our IFO 415% oversubscribed!! The vesting contracts with 4,000,000 tokens locked are released Our first staking pools are now on mainnet We added Relayer support to mainnet and unveiled plans for community relayers We started gradually open-sourcing all of our code Someone hid a Typhoon note in a smart contract on bscscan!</description></item><item><title>Adding Relayer support &amp; community relayer plans</title><link>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/adding-relayer-support-community-relayer-plans-e95a114fd0e0/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 22:23:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/adding-relayer-support-community-relayer-plans-e95a114fd0e0/</guid><description>This story has originally appeared on https://medium.com/@typhoonnetwork/adding-relayer-support-community-relayer-plans-e95a114fd0e0
We’re happy to announce that we added experimental support for relayers to Typhoon to further improve anonymity, with the first official relayer being available on the mainnet app from today. To use the official relayer, simply tick the “use relayer” checkbox (this will incur a 1% fee to the relayer wallet).
Confused what relayers are? Fear not, we’re taking a dive into what they do and why we need them:</description></item><item><title>Resolving the “wrong network” error</title><link>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/resolving-the-wrong-network-error-f47eafb768ee/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 10:10:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/resolving-the-wrong-network-error-f47eafb768ee/</guid><description>This story has originally appeared on https://medium.com/@typhoonnetwork/resolving-the-wrong-network-error-f47eafb768ee
A common issue we get asked about on our telegram, is the site is displaying “wrong network” where the connect button should be.
To resolve this, you’ll need to change your crypto wallet extension to use the Binance Smart Chain Network. Currently, we only support Metamask and the Binance Chain Wallet.
To select the correct network, click on the dropdown at the top of either wallet, and select “Binance Smart Chain Network”.</description></item><item><title>Typhoon Network Digest— Pre-IFO Edition</title><link>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/typhoon-network-digest-pre-ifo-edition-5245812d78f7/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 07:59:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/typhoon-network-digest-pre-ifo-edition-5245812d78f7/</guid><description>This story has originally appeared on https://medium.com/@typhoonnetwork/typhoon-network-digest-pre-ifo-edition-5245812d78f7
Hi and welcome to the first Typhoon Network digest, where we’ll be giving an overview of what happened in the recent days/weeks, our thoughts and what to expect next.
The last few weeks have been very hectic:
We announced our IFO with GooseFinance We published our whitepaper Our Telegram went from 10 to 1260 members Our Twitter grew from ~20 to 1012 followers We announced an Airdrop We had an AMA session with CryptoRoyals (link) Typhoon broke $5m in Volume Updates to the core system Small Improvements to privacy One things we noticed is that users didn’t fully understand how the app is supposed to work and often used the same wallet for both deposit and withdrawal.</description></item><item><title>Announcing the Typhoon Airdrop</title><link>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/announcing-the-typhoon-airdrop-a8fd5e572cc8/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 01:40:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/announcing-the-typhoon-airdrop-a8fd5e572cc8/</guid><description>This story has originally appeared on https://medium.com/@typhoonnetwork/announcing-the-typhoon-airdrop-a8fd5e572cc8
With only 4 days left until our IFO with GooseFinance, we’re working very hard on getting the service as polished as we can. We truly believe we have built something great and want everyone with a BSC wallet to give it a try and give us feedback!
Further to this, if you try Typhoon before the IFO and deposit into any of the available vaults, you’ll automatically qualify for our TYPH airdrop!</description></item><item><title>Announcing our IFO with GooseFinance</title><link>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/announcing-our-ifo-with-goose-defi-51021aa8be64/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 13:29:41 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/announcing-our-ifo-with-goose-defi-51021aa8be64/</guid><description>This story has originally appeared on https://medium.com/@typhoonnetwork/announcing-our-ifo-with-goose-defi-51021aa8be64
Update 2021–03–21: We revised IFO details such as entry price and updated this post accordingly.
We are excited to announce, we are partnering with GooseFinance to launch an IFO! The IFO will run from 26th of March 2021, 6pm UTC for 12 hours.
Why did we decide to do an IFO? Raising funds is always a tricky decision — is there a justification for doing it?</description></item><item><title>Typhoon launches to bring private transactions to Binance Smart</title><link>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/typhoon-launches-to-bring-private-transactions-to-binance-smart-9306852452fd/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 09:31:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://archive.typhoon.network/posts/typhoonnetwork/typhoon-launches-to-bring-private-transactions-to-binance-smart-9306852452fd/</guid><description>This story has originally appeared on https://medium.com/@typhoonnetwork/typhoon-launches-to-bring-private-transactions-to-binance-smart-9306852452fd
Blockchains are designed to be public ledgers: Everyone can see everything that happens on those chains, that’s just how they work. It’s very easy to open bscscan.com, type in a wallet address and see what that wallet was up to:
Where that person sent funds recently Which smart contracts he interacted with Which apps they used How much money they hold in any specific asset …and much more!</description></item></channel></rss>